Exercise 4-6, Rule 3, Bottom of the Staircase. T at the bottom of a staircase
is in the held position. By held, I mean that the tongue is in the T position, but
the air isn't released. To compare, when you say T as in Tom, there's a sharp burst
of air over the tip of the tongue, and when you say Betty, there's a soft puff of
air over the tip of the tongue. When you hold a T, as in hot, your T is in the
position for T, but you keep the air in. 1. She hit the hot hut with her hat. 2. We
went to that net site to get what we needed. 3. Pat was quite right, wasn't
she? 4. What? Put my hat back. Five. Hot. Late. Fat. Goat. Hit. Put. Knot. Hurt.
What. Set. Paint. Weight. Sit. Dirt. Note. Fit. Lot. Light. Suit. Point. Incident.
Tight.